

# CONTACT

- +91 7066603353
- ☑ niranjan.mh15@gmail.com
- Oighi, Pune 411015
- linkedin.com/in/vniranjan/

# **EDUCATION**

# 2024 - PRESENT UTTARANCHAL UNIVERSITY

Master of Business
Administration

# 2019 - 2023 YCMOU UNIVERSITY

• Bachelor of Arts

# SKILLS

- Digital Marketing
- Web Analytics
- PPC Campaigns
- SEO
- Social Media
- Content Marketing
- Email Marketing
- Lead Generation
- Conversion Optimization

# CERTIFICATIONS

- Google Ads
- Google Analytics
- Hubspot

# NIRANJAN VIBHANDIK

# DIGITAL MARKETING MANAGER

# PERSONAL SUMMARY

Being a well-seasoned Digital Marketing expert, Niranjan has helped many organizations achieve success and business growth by offering unique marketing strategies. He delivered successful results in B2B, B2C & D2C business models seamlessly throughout his career. Niranjan holds a good command over analytical skills to measure marketing results & optimize plans accordingly. A decade full of marketing experience has crafted him into an expert figure to overcome any challenge of the marketing funnel to succeed.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Decipher Market Research**

JUL 2023 - PRESENT

Digital Marketing Manager

- Develop and execute comprehensive marketing strategies and campaigns that align with the company's goals and objectives.
- Lead, mentor, and manage team of 9 members from different areas of digital marketing like social, SEO, Email & branding campaigns
- Measure the team members performance & help improve productivity with effective guidance
- Managed a high-performing marketing team, fostering a collaborative and results-driven work environment.
- Monitor goal consistency across marketing channels and creative materials.

#### iConx Solutions

MAY 2019 - JUN 2023

Marketing Director

- I owned the responsibility of growing the business with various online marketing strategies
- Helped develop marketing materials like graphics, videos, blogs & printing designs for campaigns
- Managed a team of 6 marketers to produce expected results in a given timeline & resources
- Managed website performance & tracking funnels for accurate data gathering & reporting
- Performed & managed SEO, PPC, Social Media & Email Marketing campaigns with higher efficiency.

#### **ESDS Software Solutions Pvt Ltd**

NOV 2015 - JAN 2018

Sr Digital Marketing Executive

- Perform website technical audits & work on optimization
- Execute Onpage SEO optimization for the company website
- Find new methods of SEO to improve traffic & ranking of company's official website
- Execute in-depth off-page SEO with backlink building to improve website domain authority with rank

# **TOOLS**

- Moz
- SEMRush
- Google Analytics
- Google Tag Manager
- Google Ads
- Google Search Console
- Ahref
- Meta Business Suite
- Screaming Frog
- Adobe Photoshop
- Canva
- Powtoon
- Yoast
- Wordpress
- WooCommerce
- LinkedIn Business
- Sales Navigator
- Apollo
- Mailchimp
- Brevo
- Hootsuite
- Buffer
- Zapier
- Pebbly
- Jasper
- Grammarly
- Shopify
- Zoho CRM
- Hubspot
- ChatGPT
- Compose AI
- MidJourney
- 30+ More

- Develop social content plan for official handles & share the social post with creative graphics & videos
- Ensure the growth of social media content on relevant platform in terms of engagement & conversions
- Prepare monthly analytical reports of organic & inorganic traffic in regards to its conversion

#### Xinet Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

MAR 2014 - OCT 2015

Search Marketing Executive

- Prepare a comprehensive digital marketing strategy for each project according to its industry standards.
- Perform a detailed competitor analysis and provide a unique solution based on the findings.
- Setup PPC campaigns on Google Adwords, LinkedIn & Facebook to generate lead
- Work on Onpage & Offpage SEO of Websites to improve its site authority & SERP Ranking
- Continuously track campaign's effectiveness and adjust strategies according to the market trend.

# **Application Nexus Webservices Pvt. Ltd.** MAY 2011 - NOV 2012 Search Engine Associate

- Create an effective search engine optimization strategy along with documentation & reports
- Perform thorough keyword research for e-commerce websites
- Generate a comprehensive website SEO audit to find pages with issues & technical errors
- ·Work on On-page optimization for landing pages and main category pages of the website
- Research and Develop new strategies for Off-page optimization.
- Build High PR/DR Backlinks for the website on a weekly basis.
- Make use of Google Trends to understand the demand & make changes in keywords accordingly
- Create weekly execution reports & monthly ranking reports
- Achieve expected goals within the estimated time

#### DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned information is correct, up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars.

<sup>&</sup>quot;Considering the limited space, I reserve the further skills & profile details for a personal interview."